There it is.
The old man's ship is right on schedule.
He's just about 20 minutes away.
So as far as you know, Mr.
Joestar's the only passenger on board?
He is.
The rest of the crew members are
from the Speed Wagon Foundation.
Even so,
I'm sure Chili Pepper
will try to pass over
the water and sneak
onto the old man's ship.
Despite the fact that he's
confined to areas with electricity.
If he gets to Joseph first, he'll
kill him without a second thought.
and everything we've gone through
will have been for nothing.
Hey, Jotaro!
We checked the boat over
and it's good to go!
We also checked the battery.
There's no sign of him in here.
We're ready to set out
whenever you give the word.
About that.
Only Okuyasu and I are heading
over to meet with the old man.
I want you to stay here and
hold down the fort with Koichi.
Stay here?
But you'll need backup, won't you?
Yeah, he's right!
Josuke, Chili Peppers' user,
is hiding somewhere in this
harbor watching our every move.
Understand he's laying
low right now and waiting
for us to do something
that'll give away the ship's
position and my gut's telling
me a boat won't be his
hiding place all he needs to
make it over to the old man
is a battery and something
faster than a speed boat
once he puts those two things
together he'll use it to
send chili pepper flying
to the old man's ship wait
a second are you thinking
he's gonna take to the sky?
Yeah.
To be perfectly frank, he's
probably making off with a remote
controlled plane as we speak.
That thought hadn't even occurred to me!
But it's possible.
Once they pick up speed, model airplanes
can fly over 100 kilometers per hour!
Faster than the motorboat's top speed!
And because Chili Pepper will be in control
of it, he can fly the plane as far and
as high as the battery will take him!
He doesn't need a remote control signal!
Listen, Josuke.
If If you spot anything flying around
here, I want you to search for the user.
Koichi's reverb has a range of 50
meters, so he can help out too.
If that stand gets to the ship before
we do, the old man is as good as dead.
Your job is to stay on watch and
protect your father from the harbor.
We clear Josuke.
Yeah.
From here on out, we don't
have a single second to spare.
Joestar's life is on the line.
Thank you.
Best of luck, Okuyasu.
Sing to you, Koichi.
In about 20 minutes, we'll finally
arrive at the Port of Mariah, Mr.
Joestar.
Is that right?
I seem to have misplaced my cane.
Have you seen it?
Isn't that it right in front of you, sir?
So he's my father, huh?
Josuke?
Are you alright?
I'm just processing.
I've never met this guy in my life.
Yet I'm supposed to accept
that he's my father.
I don't know, it's...
But the only thing that
matters right now is his life
is in danger if I didn't
even lift a finger to help.
I'd always regret it besides my mom
would fall apart if the guy croaked.
Damn that Jotaro if he left you two mouth
breathers behind to sniff out my user.
That means he completely saw through
my remote controlled playing trick.
There you are Chili Pepper.
I'll give this to Jotaro Kujo,
the man's sharp as a tack.
He's the last person I'd want finding me.
He'd just kill my five.
Speaking of killing,
this remote-controlled
Spitfire plane can reach
Joseph Joestar's boat
in a mere five minutes.
A dinged-up old motorboat, on the other
hand, would take about eight to ten.
Meaning,
if I can put you two down for
a dirt nap in three minutes,
it'll give me time to
catch up and pass them.
Wait, are you trying to tell
me you're Silly Peppers, user?
You're looking at Akira Otoishi, age 19.
Oh, and don't let the
guitar throw you off.
One day I want to be a rocking guitarist,
the likes of Jimi Hendrix and Jeff Beck.
That's why I keep this sweet little
mama on my person 24 hours a day,
seven days a week.
One day the masses will look
up from their mundane lives.
And they'll be lining up for miles to
let my music knock them off their feet!
People around the world will know my name.
Oh yeah?
This can't be good!
I never thought a stand user
would come out of hiding.
Which means there's no doubt
in his mind that he can
slaughter both me and
Josuke without much trouble.
I'm ready for round two with Shining
Diamond, but I'll only use my little pinky,
just like I did with Okuyasu.
You should get back, Koichi.
It's game on, Josuke Higashikata!
Just a minute. Huh?
If you're planning to use only
your pinky in this showdown,
then I've got a couple of rules of my own.
You can take your rules
and shove them, fool!
Rules are wasted on a pup kid like you!
Ah!
You damn bastard!
How dare you!
Well, you did say that
rules are wasted on me.
You also said something about bringing
me down with your pinky finger.
So what's the wannabe
rocker Otoishi gonna do now?
I'll kill you!
You already said that!
Don't you have any new material, fool?
The pain in my finger is unbearable!
I have to redirect it onto something!
This gnawing rage, I
have defense to someone!
Awesome!
First I'll kill you, then the old gas bag!
After that, your precious mommies!
That was pure ecstasy.
My heart is free again.
There's no greater euphoria than
letting your blistering rage fly.
Let's test that theory, Otoishi!
What the hell?
How'd he...
I know Stans can move at incredible
speeds, but this is different.
It's like he found a way
to teleport behind me.
No, Josuke, that's not what happened.
I was able to see everything back there.
Otoishi didn't take a single step.
You're the one who changed position.
Something moved you. Say what?
Chili peppers suddenly appeared and
flipped shining diamond around 180 degrees.
without you even realizing it.
Just look, you're facing the ocean.
Chili Pepper did that?
Where is he now, Koichi?
I don't see that sparky bastard.
He's hiding underground.
He's using the storm
drains to come and go.
He popped halfway out of the
drain to turn you around.
There must be underground electrical
lines running all over the place.
A little soul searching always gives
me the boost I need to bring the pain.
Behind you, on your right.
He's right behind you!
He bolts back into the electrical
wires at the last second,
and his speed makes him hard to pin down.
Jotaro's the only one
who can keep up with him.
What are we gonna do?
Here in the harbor,
you don't have the luxury of digging
up asphalt and severing all the wires.
Josuke Higashkata. However,
the bigger the opening you make
in the ground with shiny diamonds,
the easier it is to surface from below?
and knock your lights out!
Josuke is on your right!
No, in front!
Behind you!
No, ladies!
This is like a game of
whack-a-mole on steroids!
I can't follow his movements at
all when he's going that fast!
What's the matter, Josuke?
Can't keep your eye on the birdie!
Josuke, no!
Well, look at that.
Two minutes to spare.
That gives me plenty
of time to finish this.
Hey, Koichi, keep track of Chili
Pepper's location and call it out to me.
At this range, he's moving too
fast for my eyes to follow.
But if you can't follow
him, how am I supposed to?
As soon as I find him, he disappears.
Then you have to look harder, Koichi.
We're about to win this and by now
you should know what I'm thinking.
I should?
That muck on the ground, the
asphalt's turned into tar.
And the drains are covered
in all the oil from the tar.
I get it now.
When Josuke struck the ground, he reduced
the asphalt to its most basic ingredients.
Which means...
Behind you on the left!
Oh, yeah!
Right in the kisser!
Well, that's great.
Our strategy worked like a charm.
Guess I'm the superstar now, because
I'm gonna rock this loser's world.
Huh?
It's the boat!
He's dead ahead, Jotaro! See?
We're almost there!
Don't drop your cards yet.
Whoa!
What the hell's happening over there?
Josuke! Koichi!
What's that light?
I underestimated you, Josuke Higashikata.
I was too focused on my presentation and
should have just gone in for the kill.
But I've learned my lesson.
The juvenile me is no more.
I'm reborn as a killing machine!
And for my first act of anarchy,
I'll focus all of Morio's
electricity into Jelly Pepper.
This is my last resort.
Using this technique means temporarily
knocking out power all over town,
which I'm forced to draw
on for my lifeblood.
But none of that matters now.
After I've done away with you cretins,
I'll bolt over to the RC plane's battery,
then I'll fly over to
Joseph and slide his throat!
What the?
I can't see a thing!
Bastards!
I don't believe it!
Chili Pepper got the best of Josuke!
Josuke!
Is it sinking in yet?
This entire town's electrical
power is at my disposal.
And to really drive the point home?
I'll be sure to charge my electric bill.
for the month to your address.
It slides out, Josuke!
Is that a tire?
Just as I expected.
You were too dense to figure it out.
Huh?
Now I understand!
You blew up that tire on purpose!
It was all part of your plan
to entomb my stand in rubber!
Of course!
Rubber is an insulator, so it
doesn't conduct electricity!
Chili Pepper is powerless in there!
Damn it all!
Alright!
We just have to wait for Jojaro now!
Just kidding!
A good idea, but that's
not gonna work on me! Ha!
Your plan might have succeeded
had the rubber been a meter thick!
But this flimsy excuse for a trap
doesn't even register as a threat!
So let me show you some
real power, dumbass!
You've lost this battle, Josuke!
Just great.
You really are as stupid as you look.
Having your stand break through the tire
was the dumbest thing you could have done.
Huh?
I forgot about the air in the tire!
The pressure release
launched him like a rocket!
No!
Not the ocean!
Anything but the ocean!
Oh, yeah, that's right.
Salt water conducts electricity.
And in the ocean, the electricity that
powers him will scatter in every direction.
I'm sorry, I tried to kill you!
Please, just get me outta here!
Didn't you say something about getting
rid of your juvenile self a while back?
Sorry, that's impossible
for a lowlife like you.
I'm...
dissolving it!
His stance been completely diffused,
which means that Akira is...
Is...
is he dead?
Jotaro!
I have some great news!
It wasn't easy, but we managed
to defeat Chili Pepper's user!
Nice job.
We can breathe easier now.
So, this old geezer is Josuke's dad, huh?
He's kind of buff, but at the same time,
it looks like he's got
one foot in the grave.
You.
I don't believe we've met.
Don't just stand there.
Introduce yourself.
I'm Okuyasu, sir. Okuyasu?
I live in Josuke's neighborhood,
and I'm also a stand user.
Hmm?
I'm a stand user! Huh? Huh?
I said I'm a stand user!
Yeah, you're a second-hand computer?
I'm a stand user!
Oh, a stand user.
You young folks should really learn
to speak up and quit mumbling.
By the way, Osumatsu, I
can't seem to find my cane.
You wouldn't happen to know
where I left it, would you?
Oops, silly me.
I'm holding the damn thing
right here in my hand.
Has he lost his marbles?
Mr.
Joestar, I've come to
pick up your luggage, sir.
Huh?
If it wouldn't be too much trouble,
would you mind answering a question?
Has Josuke ever mentioned me to you?
The man who went 16 years without knowing
he had a son out there who needed him?
Has he said anything about me at all?
I hate to say it, but no, he
hasn't said much about you.
Is that so?
I guess it's to be expected, huh?
All right!
They're finally here!
Look, Josuke, do you see them?
Yeah, cool, I guess.
Huh?
If I'm being honest, I kind of wish
he'd just go home and leave us in peace.
Josuke?
It's the truth.
But don't get me wrong, I'm
glad Otoishi didn't kill him.
Now we can go back to our lives.
Well, some of us.
I've never laid eyes on the guy before.
How am I supposed to
think of him as my dad?
He's barely a stranger.
Just watch.
It's gonna be awkward for us both.
It's not like I hate him or anything.
But I have to think about
my mom's well-being, too.
You get where I'm coming from, right?
Koichi?
No!
It can't be!
Josuke!
Look over there!
His body's gone!
Jotaro, we've got trouble!
Akira Otoishi's body disappeared!
He's still alive!
What are we gonna do?
Red alert!
We've been boarded by the enemy!
Akira Otoishi is somehow still alive!
Are you kidding me?
Take Mr. Jot...
Who are you?
Hey, did you say something?
No, he...
I'm the one who said it!
I was trying to tell you that he's
not from the Speedwagon Foundation!
What the hell are you talking about?
He's the enemy!
So you're the guy I have to kill?
Wait, I'm on your side here!
I'm the one who told you about the
enemy in the first place, remember?
Would the real enemy
do something like that?
He's the one you want to beat up!
Yeah, that makes sense!
Surely you haven't forgotten I'm
the one who pointed out the enemy!
This poser came here to
throw you off your guard!
Don't fall for it!
Wait, you're making sense too!
Then the question is, who's the user?
He's the user! Damn it!
Why do I have to make
another important decision?
This is what I get for relying on my
thrill for everything all these years!
Bumping off Okuyasu will be easy enough,
and thankfully Jotaro
hasn't seen my face yet.
I just have to kill Joseph
and get the hell out of Dodge!
It'll be easy!
These half-woods will never catch me!
It's chili pepper!
That's not good! Huh?
You said you got me a smelly sweater!
No thanks!
Time to die!
I figured it out!
The stand user
HAS TO BE YOU!
AHHHHH! AHHHHH!
AHHHHH!
Nobody fools me twice!
Don't ever forget that you dumbass!
You figured out as a user how it was easy.
TELL ME ALREADY!
I was gonna beat the shit out of
both of you and sort it out later.
That deduction stuff
is for the birds! Yeah.
You should be careful.
One misstep and you'll be
going for an unwanted swim!
Right?
Sorry if I had my cane,
I could manage by myself.
But it broke a few moments ago.
It was the strangest thing.
Then I don't have much of a choice.
Here you can hold on to me.
Hey, I just had a great idea!
Josuke should have his
shining diamond fix the cane!
Do you even hear yourself, Okuyasu?
Sometimes it's like
you don't have a brain!
It is, but why?
Come on, isn't it obvious?
Just this once, it's
better to leave it broken.
But why? Seriously?
Now, if we can retrieve the bow
and arrow, it'll all be over.
And this town will be safe again.
Don't mind a magenta feeling.
Take a shelter in the face of my spine.
Straight like a Chaka cherry cola.
I don't need to try to explain.
How to hold on tight.
And if it happens again.
I'ma move so slightly.
To the arms and the lips and the face.
To the humic and the ball.
That I need to, I want to.
Come and stand a little bit closer.
Breathe in and get a bit higher.
You'll never know what hit you.
When I get to you.
Ooh, I want you.
I don't know if I need you.
But ooh, I've got to find you.
Ooh, I want you.
I don't know if I need you.
But ooh, I've got to find you.